acit-services.net 2010-12-22

# Acit Services - Privacy Statement

|  | 

| 

ACiT maintains Web sites at its Jeddah headquarters as well as at its branches abroad (listed below). **  
Privacy Protection  
** This policy establishes how we handle the information we learn about you when you visit our site. Protecting the privacy and personal data of our visitors is of utmost importance to us. Protecting your privacy and your personal data is an important aspect of the way we create, organize and implement our activities on-line and off-line.  
 **Linkages Characteristics  
** The specific practices outlined in this privacy statement apply to ACiT Web site. Other bodies/entities (such as, but not limited to, Enterwide©, Al Jeraisy©, Microsoft©, SUN©, Joomla!, etc.) linked to ACiT may have slightly different practices, though the commitment to your privacy will always be the same. You are encouraged to review the privacy statements of other bodies/entities when visiting their Web sites.   
**  
Purpose Specifications and Data Collection  
** In general, you can browse ACiT Web site without disclosing any information about yourself. If you visit ACiT Web site to read or download information, we collect and store only the following information that is automatically recognized: the date and time, the originating IP address, the domain name, the type of browser and operating system used (if provided by the browser), the URL of the referring page (if provided by the browser), the object requested and the completion status of the request.   
**  
Cookies and Other Technologies  
** As described above, we sometimes collect anonymous information from visits to our site to help us provide better customer service. For example, we keep track of the domains from which people visit and we also measure visitor activity on ACiT Web site, but we do so in ways that keep the information anonymous. We use the information that we collect to measure the number of visitors to the different areas of our site, and to help us make our site more useful to visitors. This includes analyzing these logs periodically to measure the traffic through our servers, the number of pages visited and the level of demand for pages and topics of interest. The logs may be preserved indefinitely and used at any time and in any way to prevent security breaches and to ensure the integrity of the data on our servers.

We collect the anonymous information we mentioned above through the use of various technologies, one of which is called "cookies". A cookie is an element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your hard drive. The following information is stored in the cookies:

·  IP address   
·  Session number   
·  If the user has chosen "remember login and password", those two items are encoded and added to the cookie.   
Also, when we collect personal data from you in connection with a transaction we may extract some information about that transaction in an anonymous format and combine it with other anonymous information.

This anonymous information is used and analyzed only at an aggregate level to help us understand trends and patters. None of this information is reviewed at an individual level. If you do not want your transaction details used in this manner, you can either disable your cookies or opt-out at the order or request stage.

We do not associate the information stored in a visitor's cookie with any other personal data about that visitor.

All our employees and processors who have access to personal data and are associated with the processing of that data are obliged to respect the confidentiality of data.

 **  
Visitor's Choice  
** Registering on our site is optional. If you choose not to register or provide personal information, you can still use ACiT Web site. However, you will not be able to purchase items or receive email alerts. ACiT views the customer information that it collects as a valuable and confidential asset of which we take great care to ensure its fsafety.

You may choose to register to ACIT and receive promotional or marketing information from ACiT or its centers by selecting the appropriate option when you register personal data. If you choose to register, your information will be available to ACIT Staff and to delegations for the purpose of events management. If you do not wish to continue receiving promotional or marketing information, please notify us by e-mail at

[ ](outbind://16-00000000A00669E840B84C4FBE3DAE80F158AD82642C2100/ <script language='JavaScript' type='text/javascript'> <!-- var prefix = 'ma' + 'il' + 'to'; var path = 'hr' + 'ef' + '='; var addy58559 = 'info' + '@'; addy58559 = addy58559 + 'acit-services' + '.' + 'com'; document.write\( '<a ' + path + '\\'' + prefix + ':' + addy58559 + '\\'>' \); document.write\( addy58559 \); document.write\( '<\\/a>' \); //-->\\n </script><script language='JavaScript' type='text/javascript'> <!-- document.write\( '<span style=\\'display: none;\\'>' \); //--> </script>This e-mail address is being protected from spam bots, you need JavaScript enabled to view it <script language='JavaScript' type='text/javascript'> <!-- document.write\( '</' \); document.write\( 'span>' \); //--> </script> "
 <script language='JavaScript' type='text/javascript'>
 <!--
 var prefix = 'ma' + 'il' + 'to';
 var path = 'hr' + 'ef' + '=';
 var addy58559 = 'info' + '@';
 addy58559 = addy58559 + 'acit-services' + '.' + 'com';
 document.write\( '<a ' + path + '\\'' + prefix + ':' + addy58559 + '\\'>' \);
 document.write\( addy58559 \);
 document.write\( '<\\/a>' \);
 //-->\\n </script><script language='JavaScript' type='text/javascript'>
 <!--
 document.write\( '<span style=\\'display: none;\\'>' \);
 //-->
 </script>This e-mail address is being protected from spam bots, you need JavaScript enabled to view it
 <script language='JavaScript' type='text/javascript'>
 <!--
 document.write\( '</' \);
 document.write\( 'span>' \);
 //-->
 </script>")[info@acit-services.com](mailto:info@acit-services.com)  
 **  
Disclosure  
** You may also choose to receive promotional or marketing information from other organizations. You can indicate this choice by selecting the appropriate option during registration. When you choose to receive promotional or marketing information from other organizations, we only disclose your name and address to them. However, you should note that other organizations may follow privacy practices which are different from our own privacy practices.At any time you can ask us not to further disclose your name and address by sending an e-mail to [ ](outbind://16-00000000A00669E840B84C4FBE3DAE80F158AD82642C2100/ <script language='JavaScript' type='text/javascript'> <!-- var prefix = 'ma' + 'il' + 'to'; var path = 'hr' + 'ef' + '='; var addy58559 = 'info' + '@'; addy58559 = addy58559 + 'acit-services' + '.' + 'com'; document.write\( '<a ' + path + '\\'' + prefix + ':' + addy58559 + '\\'>' \); document.write\( addy58559 \); document.write\( '<\\/a>' \); //-->\\n </script><script language='JavaScript' type='text/javascript'> <!-- document.write\( '<span style=\\'display: none;\\'>' \); //--> </script>This e-mail address is being protected from spam bots, you need JavaScript enabled to view it <script language='JavaScript' type='text/javascript'> <!-- document.write\( '</' \); document.write\( 'span>' \); //--> </script> "
 <script language='JavaScript' type='text/javascript'>
 <!--
 var prefix = 'ma' + 'il' + 'to';
 var path = 'hr' + 'ef' + '=';
 var addy58559 = 'info' + '@';
 addy58559 = addy58559 + 'acit-services' + '.' + 'com';
 document.write\( '<a ' + path + '\\'' + prefix + ':' + addy58559 + '\\'>' \);
 document.write\( addy58559 \);
 document.write\( '<\\/a>' \);
 //-->\\n </script><script language='JavaScript' type='text/javascript'>
 <!--
 document.write\( '<span style=\\'display: none;\\'>' \);
 //-->
 </script>This e-mail address is being protected from spam bots, you need JavaScript enabled to view it
 <script language='JavaScript' type='text/javascript'>
 <!--
 document.write\( '</' \);
 document.write\( 'span>' \);
 //-->
 </script>")[info@acit-services.com](mailto:info@acit-services.com)  
 **  
Individual Participation / Access  
** You can ask us whether we are keeping personal data about you, and you can also request to receive a copy of that personal data. Before sending you any personal data, we will ask you to provide proof of your identity. If you are not able to provide proof of your identity, we reserve the right to refuse to send you the personal data.

We will make a sincere effort to respond in a timely manner to your requests to the previous questions or to correct inaccuracies in your personal information. At any time, you may request that we delete or correct your personal information in our logs. For such requests, please contact 

[ ](outbind://16-00000000A00669E840B84C4FBE3DAE80F158AD82642C2100/ <script language='JavaScript' type='text/javascript'> <!-- var prefix = 'ma' + 'il' + 'to'; var path = 'hr' + 'ef' + '='; var addy58559 = 'info' + '@'; addy58559 = addy58559 + 'acit-services' + '.' + 'com'; document.write\( '<a ' + path + '\\'' + prefix + ':' + addy58559 + '\\'>' \); document.write\( addy58559 \); document.write\( '<\\/a>' \); //-->\\n </script><script language='JavaScript' type='text/javascript'> <!-- document.write\( '<span style=\\'display: none;\\'>' \); //--> </script>This e-mail address is being protected from spam bots, you need JavaScript enabled to view it <script language='JavaScript' type='text/javascript'> <!-- document.write\( '</' \); document.write\( 'span>' \); //--> </script> "
 <script language='JavaScript' type='text/javascript'>
 <!--
 var prefix = 'ma' + 'il' + 'to';
 var path = 'hr' + 'ef' + '=';
 var addy58559 = 'info' + '@';
 addy58559 = addy58559 + 'acit-services' + '.' + 'com';
 document.write\( '<a ' + path + '\\'' + prefix + ':' + addy58559 + '\\'>' \);
 document.write\( addy58559 \);
 document.write\( '<\\/a>' \);
 //-->\\n </script><script language='JavaScript' type='text/javascript'>
 <!--
 document.write\( '<span style=\\'display: none;\\'>' \);
 //-->
 </script>This e-mail address is being protected from spam bots, you need JavaScript enabled to view it
 <script language='JavaScript' type='text/javascript'>
 <!--
 document.write\( '</' \);
 document.write\( 'span>' \);
 //-->
 </script>")[info@acit-services.com](mailto:info@acit-services.com)  
 **  
Security  
** We intend to protect the quality and integrity of your personal information. ACiT has implemented technologies and security policies to protect the stored personal data of our users from unauthorized access, improper use, alteration, unlawful or accidental destruction and accidental loss. We will continue to enhance our security procedures, as new technology becomes available. ACIT employees and processors who have access to personal data are obliged to respect the privacy of our visitors and the confidentiality of their personal data.  
 **  
Personalized URL  
** ACiT provides a personalized URL (link) that brings the visitor to a personalized Web page. Such a personal URL is readily identifiable and by clicking on that link and going to a personal Web page you are agreeing to let ACiT collect information about your session visits. We use this information to help us provide you with information that matches your interests. If you do not wish information to be used in this way, simply do not sign up.  
 **  
Links  
** Throughout ACiT Web site, you will find links to third party Web sites. For example, our Web site includes a link to other companies. Please note that ACiT is not responsible for the privacy policies or content on third party sites.

ACiT Web site enables you to communicate with other visitors and to post information accessible by others. You should be aware that when you use these services, your data may be collected by other visitors.

 **  
Notifications of Changes  
** As ACiT creates new services that may generate a need to amend this privacy statement, ACiT will highlight such changes on ACiT Web site home page. You also can request the pervious Privacy Statements.   
 **  
Privacy Support  
** If you have any inquiries about our privacy statement, please contact

ACiT Services 

[ ](outbind://16-00000000A00669E840B84C4FBE3DAE80F158AD82642C2100/ <script language='JavaScript' type='text/javascript'> <!-- var prefix = 'ma' + 'il' + 'to'; var path = 'hr' + 'ef' + '='; var addy58559 = 'info' + '@'; addy58559 = addy58559 + 'acit-services' + '.' + 'com'; document.write\( '<a ' + path + '\\'' + prefix + ':' + addy58559 + '\\'>' \); document.write\( addy58559 \); document.write\( '<\\/a>' \); //-->\\n </script><script language='JavaScript' type='text/javascript'> <!-- document.write\( '<span style=\\'display: none;\\'>' \); //--> </script>This e-mail address is being protected from spam bots, you need JavaScript enabled to view it <script language='JavaScript' type='text/javascript'> <!-- document.write\( '</' \); document.write\( 'span>' \); //--> </script> "
 <script language='JavaScript' type='text/javascript'>
 <!--
 var prefix = 'ma' + 'il' + 'to';
 var path = 'hr' + 'ef' + '=';
 var addy58559 = 'info' + '@';
 addy58559 = addy58559 + 'acit-services' + '.' + 'com';
 document.write\( '<a ' + path + '\\'' + prefix + ':' + addy58559 + '\\'>' \);
 document.write\( addy58559 \);
 document.write\( '<\\/a>' \);
 //-->\\n </script><script language='JavaScript' type='text/javascript'>
 <!--
 document.write\( '<span style=\\'display: none;\\'>' \);
 //-->
 </script>This e-mail address is being protected from spam bots, you need JavaScript enabled to view it
 <script language='JavaScript' type='text/javascript'>
 <!--
 document.write\( '</' \);
 document.write\( 'span>' \);
 //-->
 </script>")[info@acit-services.com](mailto:info@acit-services.com)

|   
---|---
